Alice how many handicapped people do we
have in this office is that a trick
question we have but one I'm going to
talk like that too alas there are but
two handicapped parking spots which is
arithmetic my lady yeah you do the math
Alice what they're trying to say is that
there's no spots out there for normal
people like us all right so I'm out
there parked on the street and what I'm
supposed to what move my car in two
hours stupid get real act real Alice cuz
guess what we're here every day at 10:00
okay maybe 10:02 but when we get here
the parking lot's all packed out and
we're s so so why don't you just scratch
our butts a little bit and give us the
bonus handicap parking spot okay first
of all work starts at 9:00 yeah and see
this this is me making a note of giving
you that spot oh give parking spot to
idiots change tampon kill self change
tampon Grody that's not funny don't kill
yourself hey Anders hey what hang on if
you're parked on the street there's a
guy out there riding
tickets move it move
it